(Sheldon:)That's just as well.
They had me on hold
(Sheldon:)for 20 minutes and I hung up.
I...
(knocks) Leonard?
(Sheldon:)Also, Wolowitz invited us all
to dinner, so...
(Sheldon:)I'm ready whenever you are.
(Sheldon:)All he had was an idea.
(Amy:)Well, that is an important part.
Oh, please!
(Sheldon:)I have ideas all day long.
(Sheldon:)Reverse SeaWorld where dolphins
are allowed to pet people.
(Sheldon:)A new clothing size between
medium and large called Marge.
(Sheldon:)Snow White retold from
the point of view of Sneezy.
(Sheldon:)Why won't Doc
prescribe him something?
(Sheldon:)We finally find out.
(Amy:)But Leonard's idea was good.
(Sheldon:)Fine. Then Grumpy--
what's he so grumpy about?
(Sheldon:)Maybe his girlfriend
won't take his side.